Well, guys.
Condolences in advance.
Asshole.
Dong?
Dong, where are you?
Have you seen Dong?
Mommy?
He's downstairs.
Who the fuck is that?
Who's that?
Whoa, no way. She has the same name as Mommy!
Fancy meeting you here.
I'm sorry.
I just got emotional.
Hey, Dong, want me to introduce you to my dad too?
I'm not yet ready.
I love you, wife.
I love you so much too, Dong.
I want you two to work together to stop that plan.
I don't care about Roswell.
I still want to kill him.
Where's Mr. Ken?
Why isn't he here yet?
Why are they wearing masks?
Don't they want to be recognized?
Come with us.
Is this going to SM North?
Why aren't you answering your phone, Aemie?
Maybe Aemie's phone just died, Mr. Roswell.
You know your wife, she doesn't like charging her phone.
I have a bad feeling about this, Lamperouge.
Aren't we going to kill her yet?
Just relax.
We still have something to do.
Oh!
Zeke's an actor now!
Hey, you're awake.
Aren't you scared of us?
Why?
Are you ghosts?
You crazy woman!
You're being so mean to me, sir!
And I'm the crazy one?
You're the ones all covered up.
Even under the scorching sun.
Besides, even if you didn't cover your faces,
I wouldn't recognize you anyway.
You're crazy!
Ouch!
You're being so mean to me, sir!
What did I ever do to you?
Why did you slap me?
We're members of Yaji.
You owe us a lot!
Yaji?
Is this guy high?
He's not even in any of the profiles Zeke showed me.
Call her husband.
Zeke!
Here, talk to him.
Wife?
Zeke!
Wife, are you listening to me?
Zeke, yes, I'm here!
I'm here!
Did they fucking hurt you, wife?
Yes, Zeke!
Now that you've heard your wife's voice,
You'll do everything we tell you to do, Roswell.
Zeke!
Everything's ready.
The bomb is already planted.
He'll surely be dead in a little while.
Bomb?
There, it's almost time!
This is the end for you, Roswell!
Zeke!
Get out of there, Zeke!
Sir!
Keep quiet! We're watching, okay!
Please don't do it, sir!
Please don't do it!
Sir, just kill me instead.
Just me!
Just kill me, sir, ple—
Shut up!
Just me!
I love—
Zeke!
Bye, Roswell!
- Zeke! - Dead!
What?
Now that your husband is dead,
You're next!
You guys are terrible!
This can't be.
Zeke can't be gone.
It can't be.
You killed my husband.
Too thick.
Give me something thinner.
Thinner.
Here, Seb.
Looks like it's about to be defused, Mr. Roswell.
Lee, update.
Got it.
Here, boss.
The move is ready.
This is the end for you, Roswell!
- Zeke! - Dead!
When my wife's kidnappers call,
Play this video for them.
Copy, boss.
Woo!
It's defused, boss.
Good.
Let's go, Lee.
Send me Aemie's location.
Okay, boss.
Aemie!
Dong?
Dong, I thought you were dead.
Dong.
Boss.
We'll go ahead.
How—
How did—
How are you alive?!
I saw the explosion earlier...
It wasn't me.
What do you mean, "it wasn't you?"
It was you.
I saw it.
It was planned.
It's hard to explain.
I'm sure you'll never get it.
Does he think I'm slow?
Okay, fine.
Oh, my god!
Dong!
It was Mr. Ken!
Maybe he's still at the restaurant!
He wasn't the one who texted you.
It was...
It was—J.K. Blood.
Wasn't it Jerson Ken Blood?
Oh, it was Mr. Ken, Dong.
I talked to him the moment I found out that you went out for lunch with him.
Who texted me?
Someone pretending to be Jerson.
To kidnap you.
Oh!
Does—
Does anything hurt?
No!
What is it?!
What?
What a waste of the two-peso load I sent.
It wasn't even Mr. Ken.
Why are you laughing?
Do you have something to tell me, Dong?
Wife.
You did something very bad.
Zeke.
What happened to those men?
They're all dead.
I did that?
I'm sorry I was too late to protect you.
You ended up killing them.
Zeke, I didn't mean to.
I didn't mean to.
I thought you were dead, and everything just went dark.
I know.
I should've been the one to do that, not you.
I'm supposed to be the bad person here.
Zeke.
Thank you for taking care of me
And protecting me.
But just like you, I also want to protect the people I love.
And you're one of them.
But...
But I'm just scared.
Why...
Don't I feel guilty?
Am I a bad person now, Dong?
Don't leave me, Zeke.
Please?
I won't.
I won't think of leaving you.
Unless you want me to.
Why are you laughing?
You know what?
I should kiss you more often.
It knocks some sense into you every time I do.
You're right.
I feel like it'll be weird—
You can't leave, wife.
Huh?
Why?
You still need to rest.
I'm fine now.
I said rest.
Dong.
I've been lying down all afternoon.
Besides, I'm not tired, so I don't need to rest anymore.
Hey.
Come on, Dong.
I'm not allowed to go out, and now you're taking my phone too?
I'll answer it while you rest.
Baby Ae, I'm outside your house.
Mrs. Romero.
Zeke? Why did you answer?
Where's Aemie?
She's resting.
Mrs. Romero.
We have to talk.
Talk about what?
I'll be there in a while.
I still can't believe it.
I can't accept it.
My twin is dead.
Shan is dead.
I can't—
I don't understand it either.
First, Nico.
Now, Venice.
What's happening to our friends?
I don't know anymore.
Sir.
Do you have any leads on who killed my twin?
Not yet, sir.
My condolences.
Louie.
We'll find out the truth.
The truth will come out.
Condolences, Louie.
Stay here for now, okay?
You'll come back, right?
I will.
Just stay here.
What about Aemie girl?
I've been calling her since yesterday.
I can't reach her.
I'm getting worried.
I thought you had a plan.
Was this because of Auntie?
I should ask her if she knows something.
What is it, Cai?
Huh?
Are you saying something?
Nothing.
I'm just going to the bathroom.
Excuse me.
Where's my daughter?
She's upstairs.
We need to talk first.
Something happened yesterday.
Yes, I heard.
Have you also heard,
That she killed those who kidnapped her?
What?
Aemie?
They introduced themselves as members of Yaji.
Yaji?
Impossible.
I know how Yaji operates.
See this?
Who would send this to Baby Ae?
Well, it says Yaji.
It was given to my wife over a month ago.
Does my daughter know?
Good.
Even Shan Venice's death,
I haven't told her yet.
I think she needs to know.
But she doesn't need to know the whole truth.
She's her friend too.
She might get hurt.
I think someone's messing with us.
And Aemie is their target?
I don't think so.
I think Aemie is their medium.
And their real target...
Are Yaji
And the Roswells.
Who are they?
That's what I still need to find out.
They want to overrule?
If what you're saying is true, Roswell,
We need to take them down.
Yaji needs a queen to play her role.
They need you.
Mommy!
Baby Ae!
Didn't I tell you to stay in your room?
Mommy, Zeke won't let me go out.
Baby Ae...
Your husband is just protecting you.
Oh no.
Are they teaming up now?
Baby Ae.
There's something you need to know.
It's about your friend Shan.
Louie,
I'll call cuz again first, okay?
Come back, Momo, okay?
I'll be back.
Kevin.
Louie...
Louie!
What are you doing here, huh?
How dare you come here!
Are you happy now?
You killed my twin.
Louie, watch your words.
Louie!
Think of Venice.
Louie.
I couldn't do that to Shan.
Never mind them, babe. Let's go.
Hi, Ms. Caileigh Ferrer.
Keep your mouth shut if you don't want to end up like your friend.
Good.
Leave.
Miss me?
Why are you here?
Shouldn't I be asking you that?
Why are you here, Miss...
Guardian Angel?
Aren't you supposed to be watching over Ma'am Aemie?
What's it to you?
Oh, come on.
You need to unwind.
All you ever do is work.
What unwind?
You call this unwinding?
First of all,
I care.
Because it's my job to keep an eye on you.
Second,
I know your every move
Even how you breathe,
I know all of it.
And third, I don't like loud women.
Pssh.
Newsflash, I don't fucking care.
What do you want from me?
You're an assassin, aren't you?
How did you know?
You're giving in too easily.
I'm just testing you.
Fuck you!
I don't have time to play games with you.
You're mother is a loyal assassin of Yaji.
And you're here for your mom's last order.
Am I right?
Where did you get those lies?
Like I told you,
I know you.
Well...
You've got me all wrong.
Oh wells.
I have to go.
Until next time, Miss...
Guardian Angel.
See you never.
I heard you want to offer Roswell Corporation again
To share stocks with Stonehurst University.
Yes, but
It looks impossible for you to get what you want, dear.
We've been trying to convince them for years.
They just won't budge.
Why don't you try again?
Again and again, huh?
Market-market?
Shabu-shabu?
Oh, forget it.
You're wasting my time.
Here.
200K.
Let Aemie Romero handle the meeting.
Then why didn't you tell me sooner?
I'll call a faculty meeting first thing tomorrow.
I'm pretty close with Aemie Romero.
She's a piece of cake for me, no problem!
That's only 30% of the money I'll pay you.
You'll receive 70%...
When Aemie Romero becomes the representative of Stonehurst University.
Why is this happening, Zeke?
First Moo, then...
Now Shan.
Who's doing this to my friends?
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing, Zeke?
Do you have something to do with what happened to my friends?
Dong.
Why aren't you answering my question?
I know you're a mafia boss, Zeke, but...
I also know you can't do this to my friends.
You can't kill them.
Because you're a good person—
What if I say yes?
What if I was the one who killed your friends?
But that's only a what if, right?
It wasn't really you?
Right?
You should get some rest.
Your toy company's launching is coming up.
You need to prepare for it.
What?
Violet Swansea?
What is she doing here?
This is the beginning of a new battle between the Roswells,
And Yaji!
This is Cyd Garnett and Phoenix Strife.
Take them with you.
They're gonna be useful.
So, what's the plan?
We'll kill Aemie Roswell.
Let's go.
Zeke.
What's up, madlang people!
When I say, and 🎵whoo🎵
You say, 🎵heee🎵
That's so ugly!
Okay, again.
Hep-hep!
Ho—Hooray, say "hooray."
- Hooray. - What the hell are you doing, wife?
I'm practicing my speech.
Don't distract me.
I'm getting nervous.
Don't be.
You'll be needing this.
Oh.
Where do I put this?
Your gown has a gun pocket near your thighs.
Look.
Huh?
Hey!
Give me that.
Are you ready, wife?
Yes.
Relax.
I'm here.
Okay.
Let's go.
Mr. Guzman.
Hello, Mr. Roswell.
Thank you for coming.
Of course.
Is she the one behind all of this?
Yes.
My wife.
Nice.
By the way, this is my wife, Isabel.
Hello.
Hi.
Nice meeting you.
Hi, Isabel.
Pleasure.
Enjoy.
Yes.
Thank you.
Enjoy yourselves.
Mr. Roswell.
I'm so glad to finally meet you.
And you're?
My wife.
Congratulations then.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
Hey, sir, give me some, give me some.
Thank you.
Dong, let's toast.
Cheers.
Congratulations, wife.
Thank you, Dong.
I'm so proud of you.
Hey!
What are you doing there?
I'm working, baby.
What are you doing again?
I'm defusing a bomb.
A bomb?
Yeah.
Come here.
How can I help?
Hold this.
Don't move if you don't want us both to blow up here.
Actually,
I have one more favor to ask.
What is it now?
I need your help turning off all the lights at the event by 8:30 PM later.
Oh.
Really?
You look cute like that.
Fine, never mind.
No, no, no.
It's okay.
Auntie Alyana hired me to help you anyway.
So, I can do it.
I can do it.
Focus on what you're doing.
As you wish, baby.
I wonder where Lampe is.
Just leave him alone, bro.
He's still mourning his ex.
Told you.
What happened to you?
Boss might see you later. You're dead.
Then let him kill me.
He killed Kikiam, right?
Right?
Then let him kill me too.
Why should I care?
Hey, you.
Straighten up.
Do you know why boss did that?
Because your ex is a traitor.
And she was planning to kill Ma'am Aemie.
So enough with the drama.
Get to work!
Fuck you!
- Ha! - Alright!
Know your place, Lee, okay!
Enough! Move!
Let go of me, Boulstridge!
Fuck! Fuck!
Why is there a drunk guy?
What are you doing here?
No time to explain.
Your system was hacked.
All the communications inside this area,
They heard everything.
Who are they?
Four groups have hacked into your system, Mr. Computer Freak.
Shit.
Is this a code?
Time and location.
Boss gave that to me.
2-0-3-0 is 2030 for 830.
45 degrees south and 90 degrees west.
A road?
What does this mean?
Maybe we need to go here.
What's so funny?
Relax.
Everything is under control.
What do you mean, relax?
Different mafia organizations are inside this venue.
We don't know what their plans are.
Okay, calm down.
I know it's your job to protect Ma'am Aemie.
And don't worry.
Mr. Roswell knows what he's doing.
Why do you think
They would go through with the toy company launch if Ma'am Aemie would be in danger?
What do you need?
Who ordered you to come here?
Yaji!
Yaji?
Liar!
We better go.
The program is about to start.
How's the system?
It's back to normal.
No worries.
We need to split up.
Huh?
You're not coming with me?
No.
Someone might see us.
Okay.
Keep safe.
Miss Guar—
Fauzia.
Just call me Fauzia.
Okay.
See you.
Fauzia.
Stay alive.
I will.
Mr. Roswell. Ma'am Aemie.
Boss.
Damn!
You guys are looking handsome!
Good thing they've finally arrived.
I don't know anyone here, they're the only ones I know.
Like I've said,
Yaji is not our enemy here.
The purpose of this launch is to expose the enemy.
Shit!
Why?
We're not the only snipers here.
There are others.
I bet you came here to see your daughter.
Why haven't you joined them yet?
No.
Actually, I came here to see you dead.
Mr. Roswell.
Mr. Ferrer.
This is...
Violet Swansea.
Hello, good evening.
This is my wife, Aemie Ferrer-Roswell.
The daughter...
Of Alyana Heartily-Ferrer.
Zeke.
Mei, why don't you just stop your plan?
Are you out of your mind, Cass?
She's absolutely fine, sis.
It's already a blackout.
Mommy, what happened?!
Who did this to you, mommy?
Who?!
Mommy!
Roswell.
Wife.